{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Maintenance Contract Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40314/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40314,"taskName":"Home Maintenance Contract or Warranty Program","taskDescription":"Find a Home Maintenance Contract or Warranty Program","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Maintenance Contract Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1202,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Annualmaintenance program Warranty construction national","textMessagingName":"Hm Maint Contract","rolloverLongDesc":"A service agreement that offers valuable protection on the properties major mechanical systems \u0026 all appliances including heating, water heater, plumbing, electrical, central air conditioning or evaporative cooler, garage door opener, garbage disposal, door bell \u0026 more. Usually does not cover any pre-existing conditions.","rolloverShortDesc":"Service agreement protecting major mechanical systems \u0026 appliances.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Find a Home Maintenance Contract or Warranty Program.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Improvement \u0026 Maintenance Contracts \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":44,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Home Maintenance or Warranty Program","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Home Maintenance Contract or Warranty Program","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Maintenance Contract Project","urlName":"Home-Maintenance-Contract-or-Warranty-Program","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Improvement Contract Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Annualmaintenance,program,Warranty,construction,national,buyers,get,programs,insurance,owners,owner,warranties,builders","emcCategoryOid":-12042,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide any additional details","primaryQuestionSetId":614,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40314/":{"taskOID":40314,"originalTaskOID":40314,"setID":614,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4447,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For what kind of home do you want to buy a home warranty contract?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5721,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single family residence","answerDisplayText":"Single family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Condominium","answerDisplayText":"Condominium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6446,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Townhome","answerDisplayText":"Townhome","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3740,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Manufactured/mobile home","answerDisplayText":"Manufactured/mobile home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2118,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Duplex","answerDisplayText":"Duplex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6512,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Triplex","answerDisplayText":"Triplex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4448,"questionDisplayText":"Who Buying Warranty Contract","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who will be buying the home warranty contract?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3064,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Homeowner occupant","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner occupant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3055,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home seller","answerDisplayText":"Home seller","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3448,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Landlord","answerDisplayText":"Landlord","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4450,"questionDisplayText":"What Needs to be Covered","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What items/systems do you want covered?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2182,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrical","answerDisplayText":"Electrical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2965,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating system and ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Heating system and ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6863,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water heater","answerDisplayText":"Water heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6134,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stove/cooktop/oven","answerDisplayText":"Stove/cooktop/oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2731,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garbage disposal","answerDisplayText":"Garbage disposal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5099,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6186,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Sump pump","answerDisplayText":"Sump pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2717,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Garage door opener","answerDisplayText":"Garage door opener","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":713,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Air conditioning","answerDisplayText":"Air conditioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6834,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Washer/dryer","answerDisplayText":"Washer/dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4777,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Pool","answerDisplayText":"Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4447,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For what kind of home do you want to buy a home warranty contract?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5721,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single family residence","answerDisplayText":"Single family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Condominium","answerDisplayText":"Condominium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6446,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Townhome","answerDisplayText":"Townhome","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3740,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Manufactured/mobile home","answerDisplayText":"Manufactured/mobile home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2118,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Duplex","answerDisplayText":"Duplex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6512,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Triplex","answerDisplayText":"Triplex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5721,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single family residence","answerDisplayText":"Single family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Condominium","answerDisplayText":"Condominium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6446,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Townhome","answerDisplayText":"Townhome","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3740,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Manufactured/mobile home","answerDisplayText":"Manufactured/mobile home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2118,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Duplex","answerDisplayText":"Duplex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6512,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Triplex","answerDisplayText":"Triplex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4448,"questionDisplayText":"Who Buying Warranty Contract","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who will be buying the home warranty contract?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3064,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Homeowner occupant","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner occupant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3055,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home seller","answerDisplayText":"Home seller","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3448,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Landlord","answerDisplayText":"Landlord","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3064,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Homeowner occupant","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner occupant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3055,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home seller","answerDisplayText":"Home seller","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3448,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Landlord","answerDisplayText":"Landlord","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4450,"questionDisplayText":"What Needs to be Covered","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What items/systems do you want covered?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2182,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrical","answerDisplayText":"Electrical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2965,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating system and ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Heating system and ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6863,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water heater","answerDisplayText":"Water heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6134,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stove/cooktop/oven","answerDisplayText":"Stove/cooktop/oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2731,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garbage disposal","answerDisplayText":"Garbage disposal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5099,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6186,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Sump pump","answerDisplayText":"Sump pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2717,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Garage door opener","answerDisplayText":"Garage door opener","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":713,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Air conditioning","answerDisplayText":"Air conditioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6834,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Washer/dryer","answerDisplayText":"Washer/dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4777,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Pool","answerDisplayText":"Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2182,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrical","answerDisplayText":"Electrical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2965,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating system and ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Heating system and ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6863,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water heater","answerDisplayText":"Water heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6134,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stove/cooktop/oven","answerDisplayText":"Stove/cooktop/oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2731,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garbage disposal","answerDisplayText":"Garbage disposal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5099,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6186,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Sump pump","answerDisplayText":"Sump pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2717,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Garage door opener","answerDisplayText":"Garage door opener","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":713,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Air conditioning","answerDisplayText":"Air conditioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6834,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Washer/dryer","answerDisplayText":"Washer/dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4777,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Pool","answerDisplayText":"Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}